《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
闪电侠回来了
The Flash is back!
你怎么获得超能力的
How did you get your powers?
你不会相信的
Oh, you're not gonna believe it.
你俩想知道最棒的是什么吗
And do you two want to know the best part?
不是只有我一个
I wasn't the only one.
爱瑞丝·韦斯特  你愿意嫁给我吗
Iris West, will you marry me?
愿意
Yes.
-这不是告别  -对
- This isn't good-bye. - No.
这更像是回头见
More like, "See you later."
他就在你需要他的地方
He's right where you wanted him.
我们现在怎么做
What do we do now?
找出其他人
We find the others.
开始记录
Begin recording.
对二号目标的观察
Observations on subject number two.
姓名  丽贝卡·夏普
Name, Rebecca Sharpe.
或者她更喜欢
Or as she prefers,
这个很普通的绰号  贝琪
the plebeian sobriquet Becky.
是王字旁的琪  不是基础的基
It's Becky with a Y, not, an I-E,
三年前
也不是吉祥的吉
or an E-E, just Y.
你知道我要的是无奶的吧
And you heard me say "No milk," right?
因为我有乳糖不耐症
'Cause I am severely lactose intolerant, like...
该目标出生于佛罗里达萨拉索塔
Subject was born in Sarasota, Florida,
人生中第一次受侮辱
the first indignity in a life
充满了各种不幸
full of unfortunate circumstances.
这绝对不是豆制品
Oh, that is definitely not soy.
该目标跟她男朋友住在一起
Subject lives with her boyfriend.
马上就到  马上就到  马上就到
Almost there, almost there, almost there.
肯尼
Kenny!
我们要好好谈谈这事
We are going to deal with this...
等五分钟  或十分钟之后
in five--five to ten minutes.
更正
Correction...
该目标以前
Subject previously lived
跟她男朋友住在一起
with her boyfriend.
-我不知道  -该目标的职业
- Oh, I don't know. - Subject's occupation...
-我是不出牌呢  -赌场发牌手
- Should I stay? - Blackjack dealer.
还是出
Or should I hit?
-该目标的性格  -我不知道
- Subject's temperament... - I--I don't know, man.
我觉得你应该出牌  为什么不出呢
I think you should just hit. Why don't you hit?
-失败主义者  -好吧  我出
- Defeatist. - Okay, I'll hit.
很好  非常好
Great, perfect. And...
21点
Got 21!
中了吧
There it is. Hereh.
这是您的  先生  恭喜你
Here you go, sir. Congratulations.
-谢谢你  亲爱的  -不客气
- Thank you, sweetheart. - Sure.
-给你  -太感谢了
- There you go. - Oh, that's--that's nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来我找到了好运气
Looks like I found my good luck charm.
我的苹果马提尼
My appletini.
不不不
Oh, no, no, no.
能不能  有没有可能
Can I--can I maybe just--
给我一封推荐信呢
can I get a reference, you think?
不行吗
No?
该目标相信无论她做什么
Subject believes no matter what she does,
整个世界都会惩罚她
the universe will conspire to punish her.
再找个工作  没问题
Another job. Ow! Okay.
或者就像她在社交网页上写的
Or as she writes on her Myspace page,
"我真倒霉"
"I am jinxed."
真好  还得另找一辆车
Great! There goes another car.
没事的  不生气
It's fine. I'm fine.
该目标的自卑感说明
Subject's low self-esteem suggests
她将会很容易受人摆布
she will be easily manipulated.
等等  等等
Wait, wait!
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait, wait!
别走
Oh, come on.
等等我  太好了
I'm here! Hey, oh, yes!
谢天谢地  终于有好运了
Thank you, universe! Finally, some good luck.
你好  好了
Hi. Okay.
闪 电 侠
第四季
第三集
现在
巴里
Barry!
你在哪
Where are you?
我不知道  我找不到凯特琳了
I don't know. I lost Caitlin.
他们人太多了
There's too many of them, man.
没事  你能行的  听我指挥
No, you can take them. Just listen to me.
你只需要做一件事
You just need to do one thing.
跑  巴里  跑
Run, Barry. Run!
不是吧
Oh, come on.
他们干掉我了
They got me.
你辜负了这座城市
Oh, you have failed this city.
来这手  查得  背后袭击
For real, Chad? In the back?
活该  老头子
Suck it, old man.
等等  你们俩都死了吗
Wait, did you guys die already?
查得这小子
Well, Chad...
他刚才说
he just told us--
走吧  走吧
Come on. Come on.
我不知道现在的孩子都怎么回事
I don't know what's wrong with kids these days.
一点礼貌都没有
Churlish.
你最好小心点  查得
You better watch yourself, Chad.
下次彩弹野战再打过
Come at me at the paintball field next time.
我会打得你屁滚...
I'll kick your little--
麦康奈尔太太
Hey! Mrs. McConnell.
你好吗  查得真是个好孩子
How you doing? Chad's a treasure.
-真的  -凯特琳的椒盐卷饼
- He really is. - Pretzel for Caitlin.
爱瑞丝的玉米热狗  西斯科的两根肉肠
Corn dog for Iris, two franks for Cisco--
好极了  谢谢
Yes, thank you.
巴里的三个汉堡
Three burgers, five churros,
五根西班牙油条和六个油炸饼
and six funnel cakes for Barry.
看看这些垃圾食品  各位  真的很抱歉
Look at all of this junk. Guys, I'm really sorry.
如果不是家里的管道
If the pipes in the house
发出奇怪又烦人的声响
weren't making this weird, annoying sound,
我就会请你们去家里吃晚饭
I would have just actually had you all over for dinner.
韦斯特家嘎吱作响的管道
Squeaky pipes at the West house.
没啥好惊讶的
What a surprise.
真的吗  你们听过这种声响吗
Really? You're familiar with this sound?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你是说
You mean the--
-没错  -管道已经这样响了
- Yeah. - It's been doing that for...
-十八年吧  -没错
- 18 years? - Yeah.
每间房子都有自己的个性  爱瑞丝
Every house has a personality, Iris.
就是想让人听到而已
Just likes to be heard.
天呐  他们分手了
Oh, my gosh. They broke up.
韦克斯勒和瓦兹拉威克斯分手了
The Wexler-Waclawiks broke up.
-来真的吗  -真的
- For real? - Yes.
-好极了  -棒
- Hell yeah. - Yes!
韦克斯勒和瓦克拉威克利斯是谁
Uh, who are the Wexler-Wa-claws-wilix,
你们为什么这么开心别人的爱情完蛋了
and why are we happy that their love is dead?
他们是一对情侣  本来这个周末
They're a couple that were getting married
要在第二街的普罗皮齐奥举办婚宴的
at the Propizio the weekend of the 2nd.
就是说现在那个场地空出来了
Which means now the venue is open.
太棒了  运气真好
That's amazing. What good luck.
就是啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
现在我们只要付定金就行
So now we just have to put a deposit down.
我过去付
I'll run it over.
不用  已经付好了  宝贝
Nope, already covered, babe.
天呐  缺口警报响了  各位
Oh, God. Breach alert, guys.
我们赶紧走  赶紧走
We gotta go. We gotta go.
哈里  杰西不来吗
Hey, Harry, um, is Jesse not coming?
那个嘛
So, um...
我和杰西今晚不是要约会吗
I thought Jesse and I were having date night.
那是你想的
Yeah, that's what you thought.
先让我...  好了
Let me just-- okay.
先让我
Just let me...
好了
Okay, so...
沃利  是我
Hey, Wally. It's me.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
我一直在想一些事情
So, I've, um-- I've been doing some thinking.
然后
And--
我们俩一直都这么忙
You know, we've both been so busy...
你和地球
You and Earth--
破烂全息图
Stupid hologram.
都怪那个该死的亚特兰大塑料
You know, it's that darn Atlantean plastic.
工艺实在是粗制滥造
It's really shoddy workmanship.
-很抱歉  -这是什么东西
- Sorry about this. - What is-- what is this thing?
分手  分手魔方
Break-- breakup cube.
你们的地球上没有分手魔方吗
You don't have breakup cubes on your Earth?
这下糟了  好吧
Oh, that's not good. Okay.
好
Okay.
分手魔方就是
A breakup cube is, uh--
分手的时候用的
kind of what it sounds like.
录一段留言给你想分手的人
You know, you record a message for the person you want to--
然后选择音乐设置
the person, and you, uh, pick a music setting,
如果有需要的话  还会有纸巾弹出来
and then there's a tissue that pops out if you need that.
就是分手魔方
You know, a breakup cube.
杰西要用分手魔方和我分手吗
Jesse's breaking up with me with a cube?
这种让人心碎的方式还真是便利
Seems like a really convenient way to break somebody's heart.
没错
Exactly.
她的留言说了些什么
What did she say in the message?
你也听到了  你是个好人
You know, you heard. You-- you're a great guy--
我不记得了
I don't remember.
难道你一点也不记得吗
Don't you have total recall?
嗯  不记得  我记得
Yeah-- no, no. Don't-- I did.
我不记得  我记得  但是又不记得
I don't. I did, but I don't.
拜托  别逼我...
Come on, don't make me--
她...  你听到了
she-- you heard.
她说你是个好人
She said that you're a great, great guy
但是她在我们的地球上很忙
and that she was busy on our Earth,
而你在这忙着暂代他人...
and that you're busy here filling in for--
你懂的
you know--
你在这个地球上忙  所以她只是觉得你们俩
on this Earth, and she just felt that you guys
有些不同步
were a little out of sync.
所以她觉得她需要点时间
You know, and that she thought she needed
去做她的事
some time, you know, to work on her stuff.
不是因为你  是因为我
You know, it's not you, it's me.
也不是因为我  是她和我
Not me. Her, me.
是她  不是我  是她
Her, not me. Her.
然后她说  你知道  "我绝不会忘记你
And--and she said, you know, "I'll never forget you,
沃利·韦斯特  你相当了不起"
Wally West, because you're amazing,"
然后  就是你是她的
and then, uh, that you were her...
第一个
First.
还有些其他的东西  不重要的
And a bunch of other stuff. Not important.
所以  他很坚强的  你不需要  对吧
So--but he's tough. You don't need that, right?
你是个坚强的小伙子  对吧  韦斯特
You're a tough guy. Right, West?
-对  -对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
好...
Yeah, um...
他不想要盒子  不怪他
He doesn't want the cube. I don't blame him.
第一国家与奥沙利文银行发生抢劫
211s at First National and O'Sullivan Bank.
可能是连续作案
Could be a spree.
中城银行也在那条道上
Central City Bank's on that avenue, too.
我去看看
I'll check it out.
咱们还没完呢
We're not done.
什么
What?
抱歉  我不知道为什么应用崩溃了
I'm sorry, I don't know why the app crashed.
不过  这次算我请客吧
But, uh, this one's on the house.
找到一铜板  捡起来
Find a penny, pick it up,
然后一天都会有好运
then all day you'll have good luck.
非常准
So true.
下午好  女士
Ah, afternoon, ma'am.
确实是个好下午  保安先生
It is a good afternoon, Mr. Security Man.
千万别碰烤炉  妈妈
Please, don't touch the oven, Mom.
你等着我呢啊
Aww, you waited for me.
-我看到她了  -她正准备坐普锐斯逃跑
- I see her. - She's getting away in a Prius.
据我所知
Last time I checked,
闪电侠可比普锐斯快
the Flash is faster than a Prius.
什么鬼
What the hell?
这安保视频里是安保内容少到
That's the least secure security footage
前所未有的程度
I've ever seen.
那还不是她造成的最奇怪的事情
Yeah, that's not even the strangest thing she made happen.
我是说  我在一堆弹球上滑倒了
I mean, I slipped on a barrel of marbles.
就好像我在卡通里一样
It was like I was in a cartoon.
这可真是运气不好啊
That's some seriously bad luck.
这世上可没有运气这个东西
Yeah, there's no such thing as luck.
是吗  去告诉我的表兄赫克托吧
Yeah? Tell that to my cousin Hector.
他跟一个前任占了晦气
He got jinxed by an ex.
已经有三年找不到超市停车位了
Hasn't been able to find a mall parking spot for three years.
我们将你给我的画像通过
Hey, so we ran the sketches you made us
中城警局数据库进行了搜索  然后...
through the CCP database, and...
她的名字叫贝琪·夏普  24岁没前科
Her name's Becky Sharpe. She's 24 years old, no priors.
没前科  那她为什么在数据库里
No priors? Then why is she in the database?
因为最近三年里
Because in the last three years
她住在中城
she's lived in Central City,
她被追尾过四次
she's been rear-ended four times,
个人身份被偷两次
her identity stolen twice--
一个小偷的偷走了她的猫
A cat burglar literally burgled her cat.
好了  你看  哈里
Okay, you see, Harry?
那就是坏运气
That is bad juju.
好吧  拉蒙  你叫做运气的东西
Okay, Ramon, what you call juju,
我叫做量子纠缠
I call quantum entanglement.
离散的量子粒子是互相关联的
Discrete quantum particles are connected,
当它们纠缠在一起  会模仿同步
and when triggered, they simulate a synchronicity
这个  在菜鸟眼里  在一般人眼里
that, to the untrained eye-to the common eye--
可能看起来像是运气
could seem like luck.
如果贝琪能够影响她周围的粒子
So if Becky can affect the particles around her
以至于能够让它们相关联的粒子
in a positive way, then their connected particles
开始反方向旋转
start spinning negatively.
这样她身上发生好事时
So when good things happen to her,
她周围就会发生坏事
bad things happen all around her.
真棒  她有个幸运领域
Great, she's got a good luck field.
-她是超能力者  -但是她不可能是啊
- She's a meta. - Well, except she can't be.
我是说  她只在中城呆了三年
I mean, she's only been in Central City for three years.
是啊  所以她肯定不可能被
Yeah, so there's no way she was affected
粒子加速器的爆炸影响到
by the particle accelerator explosion.
基尔戈也不可能
Well, neither was Kilg%re.
我们都看到他的能力了
We saw firsthand what he could do.
不想老是这么重复
Not to sound like a broken record,
但是这些超能力者都是哪来的
but where the hell are all these new metas coming from?
你知道吗  也许衣服里的
You know what? Maybe the scanners
扫瞄器抓取到了些什么
in the suit picked something up.
你说你把所有数码产品去除了
You said you took all the tech out.
好吧  我留下了些
Okay, well, I left something in.
怎样  告我去啊
Okay? Sue me.
塞西尔需要我回去一趟
Cecile needs me at the house.
你们找到什么就通知我  好吗
You guys let me know what you find out, all right?
好的
All right.
-这里  -对  我看到了  好吗
- There. - Yeah, I-I see it, okay?
没错  战服在贝琪身上抓取到了
Yeah, the suit definitely registered trace amounts
暗物质的痕迹
of dark matter on Becky.
所以如果有其他暗物质意外
So if there was another dark matter incident--
我们必须尽快找出是在哪里如何发生的
We need to figure out how and where it happened, ASAP.
我来重新调整你的卫星
I'll calibrate your satellite
扫瞄和战服上相同的暗物质
to scan for the same dark matter found in the suit.
-你不能  -我能
- Uh, no, you won't. - Yeah, I will.
别碰...  别碰那个卫星
Don't touch the sat-- don't touch the satellite!
-我就要碰 -不行
- I'll be touching it. - Don't!
家里来快递了
Um, something just arrived for me at the loft.
我得去拿了
I gotta go.
什么
What?
你叫了水管工
You called the plumber.
乔·韦斯特  有那个声音我可受不了
Joe West, I cannot keep living with that sound.
这个房子...
You know, this house is, uh--
-棘手吗  -不
- Bitchin'? - No.
只是需要一些修缮
It's in need of some work.
以我专业的视角看  所有的水管都得换
In my certified opinion, you need all new piping.
会让您破费1万5千块
Now, it'll set you back 15 thou.
好吧
O-okay.
非常感谢
Thank you...so much.
我们需要考虑一下
You've, uh--you've given us a lot to think about.
考虑很多
And I mean a whole lot.
1万5千块
15 thou.
我叔祖父装修这里都没花那么多
My great uncle paid less for this whole place.
我估计得把那个储蓄罐砸开了
I guess I'm gonna have to break open the piggybank.
或者我们可以留着这1万5千块
Or, you know, we could take that 15.
作为新房子的分期首付
We could put it towards a down payment on something new.
你是说让我卖掉房子吗
You're suggesting that we sell my house?
宝贝  我只是建议
Babe, I'm just saying, you know, this is--
这房子对于我们这样一对
this is a really big place for a couple
独居的夫妇而言太大了  总会有
of empty nesters like us, and there's always
一些东西需要替换
gonna be something that's gonna need replacing.
我考虑一下  好吗
Let me think about it, okay?
考虑一下吧
Think about it.
想一想
-我会考虑的  -好好考虑
- I'll think about it. - Mm-hmm, think about it.
巴里  天呐  快转过身去
Barry! Oh, my God. Turn around!
-转过去了  -你看到了吗
- I did! - Did you see?
-没有  -你看到了
- No, I didn't see. - You saw!
我是看到了  不过也就一秒
I did...see. But just for a second.
对于极速者来说就是很久了
Which is like an eternity for a speedster.
在婚礼前看到新娘穿婚纱
You know it's bad luck to see a bride in her dress
可不吉利了
before the wedding day.
太迟了
Too late.
发生了什么事
What happened?
吉祥利来电话了
Um, the Propizio called.
我们不能在那里办婚礼了
We're not gonna be able to have our wedding there.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
别墅被烧毁了
Well, um, the villa burned down.
我估计可能是烤布蕾比赛
I guess a creme br?lee competition
进行得太激烈了
got a little heated.
谢天谢地我们还有备选计划
Okay, well, thankfully we have our backup.
没了  另一对新人早上把那里订了
No, another couple booked it this morning.
不过没事
It's okay, though. It's okay.
如果我们能够阻止邪恶的时间旅行极速者
If we can stop evil time-traveling speedsters
毁灭地球  我们就能够找到婚礼场地
from destroying the planet, we can find a wedding venue.
巴里  我们的婚礼就在6周后
Barry, our wedding is in six weeks.
会解决的  好吗
It'll work out. Okay?
任何时候  任何地方  我都会娶你
I would marry you anytime, anywhere.
神户牛肉  我的最爱
Ah, Kobe beef. My favorite.
贝琪
Becky.
这什么运气  居然撞见你
What are the chances I'd run into you?
这是你的秘书吗
Is this your secretary?
有意思了  你说她干瘪瘪的
Funny, you said she was haggard.
-不  我从没说过  -我帮你捡起来
- No, I--I never said-- - I'll get that for you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你的计划都是绕着这个傻子转的吗
Your plan revolves around this dolt?
你们这是怎么了
What's wrong with all of you?
谁把汤做得那么烫
Who makes soup so hot?
丽贝卡现在过得没有光彩
As lusterless as Rebecca is,
但她可能是所有人中最强大的
she may be the most formidable of them all.
那为什么现在不把她弄过来
Then why don't we get her now?
她力量善变的天性
The capricious nature of her powers
需要更多观察
warrants further observation.
天呐  那是活龙虾吗
Oh, man, are those live lobsters?
-给我  你别...  -别这样了  好吗
- Give me that. You're not-- - Stop hovering, okay?
-你拿得不对  -我知道该怎么看
- You're not holding it right. - I know how to read
-暗物质扫瞄仪  哈里  -依我看
- a dark matter scan, Harry. - Well, not from where I sit,
-你可不会  -说得好
- you don't. - Oh yeah, good one.
你不能去别的地方吗
Don't you have somewhere else to be,
比如伤另一个极速者的心
like breaking another speedster's heart?
抱歉来迟了  爱瑞丝和我在24小时不到的时间
Sorry I'm late. Iris and I just lost
失去了2个办婚礼的场地
two wedding venues in less than 24 hours.
-运气真差  -给我  好吗
- Ah, bad juju. - Give me that, okay?
测试  好的  这就开始了
Test, all right. Here we go.
调整
And adjust.
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Sorry. - Ah, sorry.
这这  就是这儿
Here, here. Right here.
这就是贝琪·夏普接触暗物质的地方
This is where Becky Sharpe was exposed to Dark Matter.
-这里吗  -是的
- Here? - Yes.
不可能  这是道路中间
It can't be. This is the middle of the street.
都不是个有趣的地方
It's not even an interesting one.
我的扫瞄很精确
My scans are accurate.
-你这扫瞄准吗  -我的扫瞄十分精准
- Your scans are accurate? - My scans are accurate!
那解释下为什么方圆几公里
Explain how there's nothing within miles of here
都没有能产生暗物质的东西
capable of even creating dark matter.
三周前有
There was three weeks ago.
这是我从神速力出来的地方
This is where I came out of the Speed Force.
不是  你出来的地方是常春藤城
No, it isn't. You came out in Ivy City.
不  我后来跑到那的  但我现在记得
No, I ran there after. But I remember now.
这就是我出来的地方
This is where I came out.
这就是传送门打开的地方
This is where the portal opened.
一波暗物质也和你一起冲出来了
And a wave of dark matter washed out with you.
我不敢想你创造了多少超能力者
I can only imagine how many meta-humans you created.
要我猜
My best guess?
一公交车的人
A busload.
我们创造的
We did it?
我们把暗物质带到了中城
We brought dark matter into Central City?
就是你们把我拉出神速力的时候
When you pulled me out of the Speed Force, yeah.
所有在那个公交车上的人
All the people on that bus,
我们把他们变都成了超能力者
we turned them into metas.
每次我们想做点好事的时候
Every time we try to do something right,
-总会出大错  -我们被诅咒了
- it goes horribly wrong. - We're cursed.
或许咱们应该烧点鼠尾草Maybe we should burn some sage.
美国习俗  烧鼠尾草可以驱邪
-各位  咱们没被诅咒  -你没被诅咒
- Guys, we're not cursed. - You're not cursed.
-但你们该被诅咒  -为什么我们
- You should be cursed at. - Okay, why should we
-要被诅咒  -你们该被诅咒
- be "Cursed at"? - You should be cursed at
因为你们没有咨询我
because you opened the Speed Force
-就打开神速力  -好了  我觉得
- without consulting me. - Okay, I don't think
我们不要再提
we need to rehash--
-好吧  -我的确咨询你了
- All right. - Okay, I did consult you,
原本就是你
and you're the one who gave me the calculations
-告诉我这个计算  -我告诉你
- in the first place. - Yeah, I told you not to use
咨询我之前不要使用  我原话是  "拉蒙
them without consulting me. I said, "Ramon,
咨询我之前不要使用这个计算"
don't use the calculations without consulting me."
-各位  -我听到了
- Guys. - Yeah, yeah, I heard you.
-我觉得没必要  -这就是为啥
- I didn't see the need for that. - And that's why
-你活该被诅咒  -到底什么意思
- you should be cursed at. - What does that even mean?
什么意思  意思是你是个...
What does it mean? It means you're a--
你知道不  这就是为什么
Okay, you know what? This is exactly why
我们没联系你  因为我们最不需要的
we didn't contact you, 'cause the last thing we need
就是你可恶的尖酸态度
around here is more of your salty-ass attitude.
如果你不需要我这种态度
If you don't need my salty attitude,
或许你应该自己干
then maybe you should carry on without me.
我就撤了
I'll let myself out.
你要回你的地球吗
Oh, are you going back to your Earth?
我现在就把你送回去
I'll breach you there right now.
"我现在就把你送回去"
"I'll breach you there right now!"
-我才不是那样的  -调真高
- That's not what I sound like. - That was really high.
西斯科  我知道哈里经常会有
Listen, Cisco, I know Harry could stand
那种医生对病人似的态度  但...
to work on his bedside manner, but--
你知道吗  我们不需要他
You know what? We don't need him.
我们需要的就是集中精力抓住超能力者
What we need is to focus on catching this meta.
-我说的对吧  -对  你说得对
- Am I right? - Yeah, you're right.
但贝琪看起来不像那种典型的反派
But Becky doesn't seem like one of our typical villains.
如果我们能追踪她
I think if we could track her down,
我们也许能说服她
maybe we could get through to her.
塞西尔
Hey, Cecile.
什么  我马上到
What? I'm on my way.
我需要你带我去家里
I need you to run me to the house.
你说你永远不想
You said you never wanted--
我需要你带我去家里
I need you to run me to the house.
是  遵命
Yes, sir.
怎么了
What happened?
屋顶从叮当响发展成啸鸣
The ceiling went from clanking to howling,
然后这就东西就开始顺着流下来了
and then it just started pouring all this stuff down.
是  得把水阀关了
Yeah. We need to turn the water off, stat.
好的
Yeah.
水阀在架空层里
So, the water valve is in the crawl space.
千万别去架空层里
Um, don't ever go into the crawl space.
我听到了  很清楚
I hear you, loud and clear.
巴里  太谢谢你了
Barry, thank you very much for your help.
我上楼看看去
I'm gonna go check upstairs.
天呐  怎么会这样
Man, why is this happening?
那女孩给我们带来厄运吗
That girl jinx us?
不  没人给咱们带来厄运
No, no. Nobody jinxed us.
这个房子只是
This house is just...
除了老还可以怎么说
what's another word for "old"?
-年代久远  -年代久远
- Vintage. - Vintage.
塞西尔认为我应该卖了它
Cecile thinks I should sell it.
是吗  你怎么看
Yeah? What do you think?
我觉得她说得有理
I think she's got a point.
在新房子生活会好很多
Life would be a hell of a lot easier in a brand-new house.
-听起来很好决定啊  -应该如此
- Sounds like an easy decision. - It should be.
但这个屋子有一样东西
But this house has got one thing
其他房子都不会有
no other house will ever have.
记得你们每次生日我都给你们量身高吗
Remember I'd measure you kids at every birthday?
是啊  我12岁的时候超过了爱瑞丝
Yeah. I outgrew Iris at 12.
她一直说她会赶上的
She kept saying she'd catch up.
关于你们的全部回忆和这些墙连在一起
All my memories of you kids are tied into these walls.
我怎么能放弃这些呢
How can I give that up?
你不必抛下它们啊  乔
Well, you don't have to give that up, Joe.
回忆会一直都在的
We'll always have those memories,
不管你住在哪
no matter where you live.
相信我
Trust me.
我妈妈去世后
When I came to live here
搬到这里来住教会了我
after my mom died, I learned that
重要的不是住在哪里
it doesn't matter where you live.
重要的是跟爱你的人住一起
Only matters that you have people that love you.
等等  怎么了
Hold on. What's up?
很好  好  我马上过去
Great. Okay, I'll go there now.
谢谢  我们没有倒霉
Thank you. We're not jinxed.
要是的话  西斯科就不会找到贝琪
If we were, Cisco wouldn't have found Becky.
她在吉特斯  我这就去
She is at Jitters. I'm going there now.
赢了  赢了  又赢了
Winner, winner! Another winner.
贝琪  你好  我能坐这吗
Becky? Hi, you mind if I sit here?
今天我运气好  但你完全不是我的菜
Oh, today's my lucky day, but you're not my type at all.
可以坐吗
Can I sit?
贝琪
Um, Becky,
你可能在想我怎么知道你的名字
well, you're probably wondering how I know your name.
我的杯子上写着呢
Mm, it's written on my cup.
对  好吧  但我不是因此...
Right, um, yeah, but that's not how I--
我是中城警局的犯罪现场鉴证员
You see, I work for the CCPD as a CSI.
我调查非常特别的人
I investigate very special people.
-名人吗  -不是名人
- Celebrities? - No, not celebrities.
是超能力者
Um, meta-humans.
我觉得你就是超能力者
Which is what I think you are.
我想三周前你在一辆城市公交上
See, I think you were exposed to dark matter on a city bus
被暗物质击中过
three weeks ago.
要是被暗物质击中了  我会有感觉的
I think I would know if I was exposed to dark matter.
真奇怪
That's weird.
贝琪  我知道你最近运气很好
Becky, I know you've been having a lot of luck lately.
而且你还从中城银行
And that you took some money
拿走了不属于你的钱
from a Central City bank that doesn't belong to you.
-你怎么知道的  -我就是知道
- How do you know all that? - I just do.
获得超能力让人无法抗拒
Look, getting powers is overwhelming.
我想你不知道是怎么回事
I'm sure you don't know how they work
也不知道要怎么使用
or what you should do with them.
我有些概念
I have some idea.
你真的想碰碰运气吗
Do you really want to test your luck?
挡我者  走霉运
Bad things happen to people that get in my way.
听着  犯罪现场鉴证员
Listen, CSI guy.
我这一生
My entire life has been
都是一个接一个的霉运
one piece of crummy luck after the next.
人生都有起起伏伏
Look, we all have ups and downs in life.
贝琪·夏普不是
Oh, not Becky Sharpe.
我一直都在翻烂牌
I have only ever been dealt bad hands.
但我知道
But I knew one day
总有一天老天爷会意识到自己犯错了
the universe would see it made a mistake.
到时我就会赢得盆满钵满
And then I'd have the run of the table.
我上了那辆公交  幸运女神对我笑了
I got on that bus, and Lady Luck smiled on me.
贝琪  这不是什么神在弥补计算错误
Becky, this isn't some higher power fixing a miscalculation.
你有超能力  而这能力正在影响
You have powers, and they're affecting
你身边的人  让他们跟你之前一样
everyone around you, making them feel as awful
霉运不断
as you used to feel.
很抱歉  但是
I'm sorry about that, but...
或许就该他们倒霉了
maybe it's just their turn.
或许就这一次  其他人可以体会
Maybe for once, everyone else can feel
我这前半杯子到底有多倒霉
for a second how bad I felt my entire life.
总之  你没有办法
Anyway, there is nothing you can do
阻止我
to stop me.
再见啦
Toodles.
我们该怎么办
So what are we gonna do?
不知道  我还不清楚
I don't know. I mean, I'm not sure yet.
我一靠近她  就会触发霉运
I can't get close enough to her without triggering bad luck.
讲真  那姑娘简直就是凶险星
Seriously, that girl's a hazard.
凶险星  就这个了
Hazard, that's the one.
或许那意味着霉运不在了
Maybe that means the jinx is gone.
她的超能力只在她身边有效果
Her powers only work in her immediate vicinity.
她没让我们倒霉
She didn't jinx us.
可房子还是摇摇欲坠
And the house is still falling to pieces.
房子都摇摇欲坠好几年了
It's been falling apart for years,
只是过程很慢很慢
just, like, really slowly.
而且杰西也甩了我
Well, plus, Jesse dumped me, too.
我知道  兄弟  我知道  很难受
I--I know, dude. And, you know, that sucks.
而我们要对付的是碰都不能碰的超能力者
And we're up against a meta we can't even touch.
一开始还是我们造就了她
And we're the ones who made her in the first place.
各位  你们知道你们现在多可笑吗
Guys, do you have any idea how ridiculous you all sound?
我们没有倒霉  也没被诅咒  好吗
We have not been jinxed. Or cursed, all right?
好运气自己造  对吗
We make our own luck, right?
那我们都专心想想怎么解决吧
So what do you say we focus and we figure this out?
爱瑞丝
Hey, Iris.
你在哪
You're where?
拜托
Oh, come on.
你为什么要我穿衬衣
Why did you want me to put on a shirt
-跑来葬礼上找你  -不不不
- and meet you at a funeral? - No, no, no.
我想要你来看看这座教堂
I wanted you to meet me at this church.
-什么  -我们在这结婚
- What? - We're getting married.
-来  把这个戴上  -什么
- Here, put this on. - Excuse me?
巴里  我们之前简直倒霉透了  对吗
Barry, we've had the worst luck, okay?
经历了支配者到萨维塔再到大猩猩
From the Dominators to Savitar to gorillas
现在又出现了这些公交车上的超能力者
and now these bus metas.
而且除此之外  我们还被诅咒了
And on top of everything else, now we're cursed.
-爱瑞丝  我们没被诅咒  -巴里
- Iris, we're not cursed. - Barry, look.
你说你随时随地都愿意娶我
You said that you would marry me anytime, anyplace.
-等等  这是  -对吗
- Well, this is-- - Right?
而我就觉得如果我们现在不结婚
And I just feel like if we don't get married now,
-恐怕永远结不了了  -才不会  好吗
- it's never gonna happen. - That's not true, okay?
-我是说  -轮到我们了
- I mean-- - Oh, it's our turn.
到我们了  赶紧  快快快
Our turn. Go, go, go, go, go.
-抱歉  抱歉  -抱歉  劳驾
- Sorry, sorry. - Sorry, excuse me.
仪式很隆重肃穆
Beautiful service.
-非常遗憾  -我超喜欢这具棺材
- So sorry. - I love this coffin.
-是杉木的吗  -来吧  快点
- Is that cedar? - Hey, let's--come on.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
-有什么能效劳的吗  -有的
- Can I help you? - Uh, yes.
我们俩想结婚
We would like to get married.
是的  没错
Yes, we would.
就现在
Right now.
能给我们一点时间
Well, would you give us a moment
重新布置一下圣坛吗
to, reset the altar?
不  不用了  不必麻烦了
Oh, no, no, that won't be necessary.
瞧  我们只要  瞧好了
Look, we'll just--watch. Watch.
-好了  -我们只要
- Okay. - We'll just...
好了
Okay.
她有点兴奋  抱歉
She's excited. Sorry.
把遗照翻过去
Flip that around.
是的  大概或许不应该这么做
Yeah, probably shouldn't have done that.
我知道  没事的
I know, it's fine.
好了  我们今天来此是为了参加
Okay. We are here today to join...
-你的名字  -我
- That's you. - Me?
巴塞洛缪·亨利·艾伦
Bartholomew Henry Allen.
-和  -爱瑞丝·安·韦斯特
- And-- - Iris Ann West.
迈向神圣的婚姻殿堂
In holy matrimony.
-抱歉  -你还好吗
- Excuse me. - You okay?
天呐
Oh, my God.
詹姆森
Jameson!
凯文  你是不是用了肉桂熏香
Kevin, did you use the cinnamon incense?
你明知他对肉桂过敏
You know he's allergic to it.
真可恶
Shame on you.
我不清楚是不是要去说这孩子  但是
I don't know if we need to shame the little boy, but--
不要紧  没事的  咬咬牙就忍过去了
No, you're fine. You're fine. Walk it off.
神父
Father...
-没事  -没有这么倒霉吧
- It's fine. - That did not just happen.
你知道吗  刚刚真是一场
You know, it was a...
非常庄重的葬礼
very nice funeral.
认真的吗  巴里
Really, Barry?
太漂亮了
That was golden.
别开枪  好吗
Don't shoot, okay?
我是来道歉的
I'm here to apologize.
我知道你是在试图帮助我们擦屁股
I know you're trying to help us fix our own colossal screw up.
-是的  一如既往  -没错  我知道
- Yeah, like always. - Yeah, I know.
我意思是  我其实都以为你现在应该到家了
I mean, I actually thought you'd be at home by now,
但你还在这埋头苦干
but here you are working away.
其实吧
Well...
地球二上的情况有点复杂
things are a little complicated on Earth-2.
杰西一切都好吗
Everything okay with Jesse?
是的  我是说  很好
Yes. I mean, yes.
如果你一定要知道的话  我花了一整个夏天
If you must know, I spent the summer
给她召集了一队人马  所以
assembling a support staff for her, so--
就像快客小队一样吗
Oh, like a Team Quick?
-不  -杰西小队
- No. - Team Jesse.
-不是  -杰西和急速者
- No. - Jesse and the Quicksters.
-他们不叫这名  -那真应该用这个名字
- They're not called that. - Well, they should be.
听起来像个超赞的小队
That sounds like an awesome team.
确实是个超赞的小队  因为是我召集的
It is an awesome team, because I assembled it.
然而之后杰西离开了并把我踢出了小队
But then, Jesse goes and kicks me off the team, all right?
显然我太像我自己了  鬼知道这话什么意思
Apparently I'm too much like me, whatever that means.
我逼她逼的太紧了  你知道的  太多测试
I push too hard. You know, too many tests.
太多训练课程
Too many training sessions.
我没给小队成员留足够的时间
You know, I don't allow the team enough time
让他们彼此联络感情
for their personal bonding.
我不理解千禧一代
I don't understand millennials.
总之  他们投票表决把我踢出去了
Anyway. They took a vote. I'm out.
我现在都无家可归了
I don't even have a home to return to now.
我甚至都无法回到我自己的地球
I can't even go back to my own Earth.
我相信你是有同感的  对吗  拉蒙
I'm sure you can empathize, right, Ramon?
因为你知道我是什么样的人
Because you know what I'm like. Well, you know what?
我们会搞定夏普的
We'll handle Sharpe,
然后我就不烦你了
and then I'll be out of your hair.
伙计们  全城各处都有低概率事件发生
Guys, there are low probability events happening all over the city.
贝基的量子场在不断扩张
Becky's quantum field is expanding.
好了  这不可能
Okay, that's not possible.
她的超能力是小范围的
Yeah, no, her powers are localized.
不再是了
Not anymore.
宝贝你在里面吗  门卡住了
Babe, you in there? The door's jammed.
马上来
One sec.
各位  量子场增强了
Guys, the quantum field is getting higher.
我朋友说你很倒霉  先生
My pals said you were bad luck, sir,
但我在想  一个机师两次遇到
but I figure, what are the odds
鸟飞进他的引擎的概率是多少呢
a pilot has a goose fly into his engine twice?
与鸟相碰
Bird strike.
求救  512航班呼叫塔台
Mayday, this is Flight 512 to tower.
一个引擎失灵  正在往下降
Lost an engine and are coming down.
什么时候危险女变得这么强大
When did Hazard get so powerful?
每个作用力都有与之相等的反作用力
Every action has an equal and opposite reaction, so--
她经历越多好运
The more good luck she experiences,
她就传播更多厄运
the more bad luck she spreads.
她现在肯定是达到了极值水平的好运
She must be experiencing an extreme level of good luck
她的量子场才能增强成这样
for her quantum field to be expanding like this.
-她现在在哪里  -她继续干活去了
- Where is she now? - She went back to work.
两点
Snake eyes!
第37次了
For the 37th time.
你赢的钱有
Bringing your winnings to 1.2...
一百二十万了
Million.
快把筹码给我吧
Give me those babies.
好吧
Hi. Okay.
再来一把  来啦
Here we go. Oh, come on, Mama.
各位  如果贝基继续赢
Guys, if Becky keeps winning,
厄运就会一直传播出去
then bad luck will keep spreading.
这可能会毁掉整座城市
This could destroy the whole city.
-好吧  冷静一下  -冷静一下
- Okay, keep calm, all right? - Keep calm.
这里没出什么毛病
Nothing's going wrong here.
各位  粒子加速器重新开启了
Guys, the particle accelerator turned back on.
它会爆炸
It's gonna explode.
粒子加速器还有四分钟激活
Four minutes to particle accelerator activation.
哈利  西斯科  汇报情况
Harry, Cisco, status report.
发电机自己开启了
The generators turned themselves on.
我们得关掉它们
We got to shut 'em down.
512航班呼叫塔台
Flight 512 to tower,
我们在尝试水上降落
we are attempting a water landing.
塞西尔
Cecile!
该死
Damn it.
巴里  你得找到危险女
Barry, you've got to find Hazard.
我快到赌场了
I'm almost at the casino.
危险女的量子场还在增强
Hazard's quantum field is increasing.
-会变得多糟  -你好  我的老朋友
- How much worse can it get? - Hello, my old friend.
让我们继续连胜吧
Let's keep this winning streak going, shall we?
好吧  樱桃
Yes. Okay, Cherry.
来了  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃
Here we go, cherry. Cherry, cherry, cherry.
樱桃  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃
Cherry, cherry, cherry, Cherry. Cherry.
樱桃  樱桃
Cherry! Cherry.
是樱桃  给我吧  给我吧
It's a cherry. Give it to me, give it to me.
樱桃  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃  樱桃
Cherry, cherry, cherry, cherry, cherry.
怎么可能会那样
How is that even possible?
等下  不
Wait, no!
右舷扇叶刚刚破裂了
Starboard fan blades just disintegrated.
我们没法到水上降落
We're not gonna make it to the water.
-巴里  怎么回事  -她在玩老虎机
- Barry, what happened? - Well, she's playing the slots,
还有  我把自己铐住了
and, I cuffed myself.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
不  我知道  得赶紧取下来
Yeah, no, I know. We need to get 'em off.
我的超能力被抑制住了
They're dampening my powers.
是是是  我在努力
Yes, yes, yes. I'm trying.
氢粒子开口  得封起来
The hydrogen particle hatch. We need to seal it.
来了
There you go.
樱桃出现
Cherry bang bang.
樱桃出现  樱桃
Cherry bang bang, cherry.
樱桃出现
Cherry bang bang!
-是两串樱桃  -快点
- That's two cherries. - Come on.
看  是闪电侠
Hey, look. It's the Flash.
不不  没有火警
No, no, hey. There's no fire.
没有火警  有人触发警报了
There's not a fire! Someone set off the alarm.
冷静
Calm down!
-宝贝  你没事吧  -我想是的
- Babe, you okay? - I think so.
该死  去后面
Damn it, out back.
-去后面  小心  -好吧
- Out back, out back. Be careful. - Okay, okay.
还有一分钟激活
One minute to activation.
能搞定
Got it.
-不  -搞不定
- Nope. - Don't got it.
电子开口也被打开了
That just opened up the electron hatch.
是  我很燃  我知道
Yes, I am on fire. I know.
没有着火
There's no fire!
加油  加油  樱桃跳出来
Come on. Come on, cherry pop.
樱桃跳出来  樱桃  樱桃跳出来  樱桃
Cherry pop, cherry. Cherry pop, cherry.
该死
Damn!
巴里  我解不开手铐
Barry, I can't get the cuffs off.
现在你还要把我拉出来
Now we got a sign to get off of me, too.
第三串樱桃  樱桃跳出来  跳出来
Cherry number three, pop cherry, pop.
即将冲撞  即将冲撞
Brace, brace, brace!
-还有30秒激活  -不行  不行
- 30 seconds to activation. - Nope, nope.
你在干什么  赶紧的
What are you doing? Come on.
不  慢着
No, wait. Wait.
-放手吧  -什么
- Let it go. - What?
-让加速器开启  -哈利
- Let the accelerator turn on. - Harry--
让加速器开启  相信我
Let the accelerator turn on. Trust me.
-还有10秒激活  -就是这样
- Ten seconds to activation. - This is it.
最后一串
Last one.
五  四  三  二...
Five, four, three, two...
来了
Here we go.
樱桃跳出来  樱桃
Cherry pop, cherry.
不  什么
No. What?
星星  不  我不明白
Star? No, I--I don't understand.
我输了
I lost?
右舷推力恢复
The starboard thrusts are alive.
-我们能成功  -很好
- We're gonna make it. - Good.
怎么回事
What just happened?
氢电子碰撞释放出暂时抵消
The hydrogen electron collision released a charge
危险女量子场的电荷
that temporarily negated Hazard's quantum field.
我们做到了
We did it.
你做到了
You did it.
你怎么知道要这么做
How did you know to do that?
蒙到的
Lucky guess.
好吧  你好
Okay. Hi.
-你好  -你能不能
- Hi. - Is there, like,
别逮捕我呢
any chance that you're not gonna arrest me?
不能  我明白
No? I understand.
-来吧  -当然
- Come on. - Sure.
好吧
Okay.
-好吧  -走这边
- Okay. Yep. - Right this way.
拉蒙
Ramon...
我应该跟你道歉
I owe you an apology.
好吧
Okay.
-就那样  -好吧
- No, that was it. - Okay, all right.
这么说怎么样
How about something like...
我很抱歉我全部都怪你身上
I'm sorry for blaming everything on you?
或者  我很抱歉我咒骂你了
Or, I'm sorry for 'cursing at' you.
挺好的  挺好的  好吧
Yeah, that's good. That's good, that--yeah.
就当我那么说了
Pretend I said that.
好吧  那我只能勉强收下了
Guess I'll take it where I can get it.
好吧  聊得不错
All right. Good talk.
你不必回地球二去
You don't have to go back to Earth-2.
-什么  -今天你拯救了世界
- What? - You saved the day.
所以你不用再进监狱了
That's your get out of jackass jail free card.
而且  你是家人
Plus, you're family.
你在这永远有个家
You'll always have a home here.
谢谢  我...
Thank you, I...
我很感激这份情感  只是...
I appreciate the sentiment. It's just that...
-这不是我的世界  -所以地球二是咯
- This is not my world. - Oh, and Earth-2 is?
你在那里交了很多我不知道的朋友吗
Did you make a bunch of friends there that I don't know about?
他们都是剪了难看发型的
What, are they all tall, brooding dudes
高大静思家伙吗
with bad haircuts?
我有...
I have--
我有同事
I have colleagues.
工作上的同事  而且
Work colleagues. And...
-有些人我并不讨厌  -正是我的观点
- some of them I don't dislike. - Exactly my point.
你花太多时间在担心杰西
You've spent so much time worrying about Jesse
还有跟死人说话  你没有停下来
and talking to dead people that you've never even stopped
过自己的生活
to make a life for yourself.
你在说什么  拉蒙  你是在说
What are you saying, Ramon? Are you literally saying
我没有自己的生活
I don't have a life?
我就是那个意思
That's exactly what I'm saying.
你没有自己的生活
You don't have a life.
但你可以创造一个
But you can make one.
在这里跟我们一起
With us, right here.
我们会帮你
We'll help you.
天知道你需不需要帮助
'Cause God knows you're gonna need that help.
-我不那么认为  -我也不那么认为
- I don't think so. - I don't think so, either.
贝基被关在铁山监狱的超能力者区
Becky is locked up in the meta wing at Iron Heights.
感觉我们的厄运
Something tells me our bad luck streak
-结束了  -很好
- has come to an end. - Good.
我们不能承受这里第三次被炸开
We can't afford to blow this place up a third time.
看看这些卫星扫瞄出来的热点
So, look at these heat scans taken from the satellite.
-这是三周前的  -那是中城巴士
- This is three weeks ago. - It's a Central City bus?
-那是巴士  -那是巴士
- That's the bus? - That's the bus.
每个热点代表一个人体
Each of these heat scans indicates a human body.
12个标记  12个超能力者
12 markers, 12 metas.
现在我们不知道有多少
Now that we know how many there are,
我们不必等他们来找我们
we won't have to wait for them to come to us.
我们可以直接去找他们
We can go right to them.
-好吧  搞定两个了  -是的
- Well, two down. - Yep.
-我们能搞定  -是的
- We got this. - Yeah, you do.
怎么了  沃利
What's wrong, Wally?
你们来告诉我  我是说...
You guys tell me. I mean...
整座城市差点炸开了
the city was about to blow up.
没人发现我不在这里
No one realized I wasn't here.
-你去哪了  沃利  -我去了地球二
- Where did you go, Wall? - I went to Earth-2.
我得找杰西说话  听她的想法
I had to talk to Jesse. Hear it from her.
她说她要专注在自己的事情  我明白
She told me she needs to focus on herself, and I get it.
我也认为我要那么做  好吗
And I think I have to do the same, right?
所以...
So...
我要离开中城
I'm leaving Central City.
你要去哪里
Where--where are you going?
我要去跟
I'm gonna go stay with a friend
蓝谷的朋友住一阵
in Blue Valley for a while.
每个英雄都有自己的旅程
Every hero has their own journey.
如果这一趟能把你带上新的道路
If yours is taking you on a new path,
你不去就对不起自己了
you owe it to yourself to go.
祝好运
Good luck.
闪电小子
Kid Flash.
没有什么比你
I don't want anything more
找到你想要的东西更重要
than for you to find what you're looking for.
但我...
But I've...
但我一直在你的人生中缺席
I've spent so much time without you in my life.
我不想失去你
I don't want to lose you.
你永远都不会失去我  爸爸
You'll never lose me, Dad.
而且  我是个极速者
Plus, I'm a speedster.
你需要我  我就跑过来
You need me, and I'll come running.
-爱你  儿子  -我也爱你
- Love you, son. - Yeah. Love you.
你确定吗
You sure?
是的
Yeah.
那就别忘记  中城永远都是
Well, don't forget, Central City will always
闪电小子的家
be the home of Kid Flash.
我不会的
I won't.
-不要当陌生人  -我不会
- Don't be a stranger. - I won't.
-我爱你  -我更爱你
- I love you. - I love you more.
好吧
Okay.
韦斯特离去
West leaves,
艾伦回来
Allen returns.
韦斯特离开  去和来
West leaves. Move, counter move.
你在说什么
What's your point?
简单来说
Simply that...
神秘的陌生人来到这里
a mysterious stranger comes to town,
寻找闪电侠
seeks out the Flash--
所以我们打开了神速力
Causes us to open the Speed Force.
造出了十几个新的超能力者
Which causes the creation of a dozen new metas.
-没错  -慢着
- Right. - Hold on.
你认为搞出武士机器人的幕后黑手
You think the guy behind the Samurai Robot--
-机士  -你认为他是想要我们
- Samuroid. - You think he wanted us
造出一车超能力者
to create a busload of metas?
我认为全都是有联系的
I think it's all connected.
为什么有人要造出超能力者
Why would anyone want to create metas?
我不知道
I don't know.
不管他们是谁  这些人
Whoever they are, they've got
都有严重的扭曲思想
a seriously warped way of thinking.
他们找到目标的速度比我们想像得快
They identified the targets sooner than we planned.
也许他们比你认为得还要聪明
Perhaps they're smarter than you gave them credit.
也许吧
Perhaps.
但我更聪明
But I'm smarter.
我还以为现在回家很安全呢
Just when I thought it was safe to get back in the house.
我可能不像你
I may not be a craftsman expert
有工匠大师的手艺  但我可以
such as yourself, but I can handle plastering
给墙的一些小洞涂灰泥
a couple of holes in the wall.
宝贝  你不必...  你不必这么做
Baby, you didn't have to-- you didn't have to do this.
这是我们的家  现在这里是个灾区
Oh, this is our home, and it is a disaster zone
我在尽一份力
right now, so I am doing my part
-把它弄好  -好吧  我很感激
- to fix it up. - Well, I appreciate that.
但  小塞西尔
But, little Cecile...
你说得对
you were right.
我是时候放开这里了
It's time for me to let this place go.
我花了一些时间才做到
I... it took me a minute to get there.
我不太能接受改变  你知道的
I'm not good with change. You know that.
但当我接受时  我发现
But once I did, I realized that
不管跟你在怎样的屋子  我都会喜欢
whatever house I'm in with you, I'm gonna love.
所以我们不妨买个洗碟机吧
So we might as well get one with a dishwasher.
还有热水浴缸
And a Jacuzzi.
热水浴缸
Jacuzzi.
我爱你
I love you.
挺有意思的  宝贝
Funny thing, babe.
其实我改变了心意
I've actually had a change of heart.
什么
What?
你要留下  真的吗
You want to stay? Really?
是的
Yeah.
你告诉我你无法找到更好的地方
You told me that you couldn't have asked for a better place
养育孩子  使我
to raise your kids, and it made me
用新的目光看这间屋子
look at this house with new eyes.
尤其是在我发现...
Especially after I found out...
乔
Joe...
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
乔
Joe?